unibank.com 2015-09-07

# Privacy Policy

 Rev 8/2014

  **FACTS**

| 

**WHAT DOES UNIBANK DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
  
---|---  
  
 Why?

| 

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
  
 What?

| 

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:

?  Social Security number and address

?  Account balances and payment history

?  Credit history and credit scores  
  
 How?

| 

All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons UniBank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.  
  
**Reasons we can share your personal information**

| 

**Does UniBank share?**

| 

**Can you limit this sharing?**  
  
---|---|---  
  
**For our everyday business purposes** **—** such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus

| 

**YES**

| 

**NO**  
  
**For our marketing purposes** **—** to offer our products and services to you

| 

**YES**

| 

**NO**  
  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies**

| 

**YES**

| 

**NO**  
  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes** **—** information about your transactions and experiences

| 

**YES**

| 

**NO**  
  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes** **—** information about your creditworthiness

| 

**YES**

| 

**YES**  
  
**For affiliates to market to you**

| 

**YES**

| 

**YES**  
  
**For nonaffiliates to market to you**

| 

**NO**

| 

**WE DO NOT SHARE**  
  
To limit 

our sharing

| 

·         Call ( **800) 578-4270** to speak with a representative **or**

·         Mail the form **** below

 **Please note:**

If you are a _new_ customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are _no longer_ our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.  However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.   
  
---|---  
  
Questions?

| 

Call (800) 578-4270 to speak with a representative.  

 Mark any/all you want to limit:

 Do not share information about my creditworthiness with your affiliates for their everyday business purposes.

 Do not use my information for affiliate marketing purposes.  
  
---  
  
**Name**

|  | 

  **Mail to:**

UniBank

Attn: Operations Department

49 Church St.

Whitinsville, MA 01588  
  
**Address**

|   
|   
  
**City, State, Zip**

|   
  
**Account #**

|   
  
**Who we are**  
  
---  
  
**Who is providing this notice?**

| 

**UNIBANK**  
  
**What we do**  
  
**How does** **UniBank** **protect my personal information?**

| 

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with state and federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.  
  
**How does** **UniBank** **collect my personal information?**

| 

We collect your personal information, for example, when you

§  open an account or deposit money

§  pay your bills or apply for a loan

§  use your credit or debit card  
  
**Why can’t I limit all sharing?**

| 

Federal law gives you the right to limit only

§  sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes — information about your creditworthiness

§  affiliates from using your information to market to you

§  sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you 

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.  
  
**What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?**

| 

Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.  
  
**Definitions**  
  
---  
  
**Affiliates**

| 

Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

·          _UniPayDirect, Inc. UniBank Fiscal Advisory Services, Inc., and Sterling Associates_  
  
**Nonaffiliates**

| 

Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. 

·          _Nonaffiliates we share with can include financial and nonfinancial services companies._  
  
**Joint marketing**

| 

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you. 

·          _Our joint marketing partners include financial service companies._  
  
Click Here for the pdf version of the UniBank Opt Out Form
